corsaforex.com 2015-03-18

# Corsa Capital

Corsa Capital Investments, Corp. ("Corsa Capital") respects each individual's right to privacy. We value our relationship with you, and we take pride in maintaining loyalty and respect with each individual client by providing you with security. The provisions of this notice apply to former clients as well as our current clients. 

## PERSONAL INFORMATION

When you apply for or maintain a live or demo account with Corsa Capital, we collect personal information about you for business purposes, such as evaluating your financial needs, processing your requests and transactions, informing you about products and services that may be of interest to you, and providing client service. Such information may include:

  * Application Information - Information you provide to us on applications and other forms, such as your name, contact info, mailing address, birth date, occupation, assets, and income.
  * Transaction Information - Information about your transactions with us and with our affiliates as well as information about our communications with you. Examples include your account balances, trading activity, your inquiries and our responses.
  * Verification Information - Information necessary to verify your identity such as a passport or drivers license. Examples also include background information about you we receive from public records or from other entities not affiliated with Corsa Capital. The Anti-Money Laundering Policy requires us to collect information and take actions necessary to verify your identity.
  * Information about your subscriptions, such as signal, alert, news category and price subscriptions.

## ABOUT COOKIES

Corsa Capital uses Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption technology in order to protect certain information that you submit. This type of technology protects you from having your information intercepted by anyone other than Corsa Capital while it is being transmitted to us. We work hard to ensure that our websites are secure and that they meet industry standards. We also use other safeguards such as firewalls, authentication systems (e.g., passwords and personal identification numbers) and access control mechanisms to control unauthorized access to systems and data.

## SECURITY TECHNOLOGY

Corsa Capital uses Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption technology in order to protect certain information that you submit. This type of technology protects you from having your information intercepted by anyone other than Corsa Capital while it is being transmitted to us. We work hard to ensure that our websites are secure and that they meet industry standards. We also use other safeguards such as firewalls, authentication systems (e.g., passwords and personal identification numbers) and access control mechanisms to control unauthorized access to systems and data.

## SHARING INFORMATION WITH OUR AFFILIATES

We may share personal information described above with our affiliates for business purposes, such as servicing client accounts and informing clients about new products and services, and as permitted by applicable law. Our affiliates may include companies controlled or owned by us as well as companies which have an ownership interest in our company. The information we share with affiliates may include any of the information described above, such as your name, address and account information. Our affiliates maintain the privacy of your information to the same extent Corsa Capital does in accordance with this Policy.

## SHARING INFORMATION WITH THE THIRD PARTIES

Corsa Capital does not disclose your personal information to third parties, except as described in this Policy. Third party disclosures may include sharing such information with non-affiliated companies that perform support services for your account or facilitate your transactions with Corsa Capital, including those that provide professional, legal, or accounting advice to Corsa Capital. Non-affiliated companies that assist Corsa Capital in providing services to you are required to maintain the confidentiality of such information to the extent they receive it and to use your personal information only in the course of providing such services and only for the purposes that Corsa Capital dictates. We may also disclose your personal information to third parties to fulfill your instructions or pursuant to your express consent. We want you to know that Corsa Capital will not sell your personal information.

## REGULATORY DISCLOSURE

Under limited circumstances, Corsa Capital may disclose your personal information to third parties as permitted by, or to comply with, applicable laws and regulations. For example, we may disclose personal information to cooperate with regulatory authorities and law enforcement agencies to comply with subpoenas or other official requests, and as necessary to protect our rights or property. Except as described in this privacy policy, we will not use your personal information for any other purpose unless we describe how such information will be used at the time you disclose it to us or we obtain your permission.

## OPT OUT

You are not required to supply any of the personal information that we may request. However, failure to do so may result in our being unable to open or maintain your account or to provide services to you. While we make every effort to ensure that all information we hold about you is accurate, complete and up to date, you can help us considerably in this regard by promptly notifying us if there are any changes to your personal information.

If you do not wish to have your personal information disclosed to third parties as described in this Policy, please contact us via e-mail at: [clients@corsaforex.com](mailto:clients@corsaforex.com) or send your request to:

Corsa Capital Investments, Corp.  
P.O. Box 3321, Drake Chambers, Road Town  
Tortola, British Virgin Islands

FOREX quotes

EURUSD 1.0613 0.19%  
  
---  
  
GBPUSD 1.4670 -0.53%  
  
USDJPY 121.20 -0.09%  
  
USDCHF 1.0020 -0.36%  
  
USDCAD 1.2793 0.06%  
  
EURJPY 128.62 0.08%  
  
EURCHF 1.0635 -0.18%  
  
GBPJPY 177.79 -0.63%  
  
GBPCHF 1.4699 -0.90%  
  
GOLD 1147.46 -0.19%  
  
#AA 13.05 -1.76%  
  
#AAPL 127.02 1.76%  
  
#ADBE 79.62 1.67%  
  
#AIG 55.78 -0.23%  
  
#AMD 2.75 0.36%  
  
#AMZN 371.88 -0.33%  
  
#AXP 81.03 -0.58%  
  
#BA 154.49 0.54%  
  
#BAC 16.06 -0.31%  
  
#BK 41.11 0.22%  
  
#C 53.83 0.30%  
  
#CAT 78.42 -1.91%  
  
#CL 42.25 -1.02%  
  
#CSCO 28.13 -0.53%  
  
#DD 74.62 -3.24%  
  
#DIS 106.97 -0.32%  
  
#EBAY 59.48 -0.10%  
  
#F 16.38 -0.61%  
  
#GE 25.31 -0.55%  
  
#GOOG 550.64 -0.61%  
  
#HD 115.58 -0.75%  
  
#HON 102.21 -0.55%  
  
#HPQ 32.42 0.22%  
  
#IBM 156.84 -0.01%  
  
#INTC 30.58 -0.75%  
  
#IP 54.73 -0.16%  
  
#JNJ 99.84 -1.19%  
  
#JPM 61.61 -0.36%  
  
#KO 40.51 0.59%  
  
#KRFT 61.69 -0.53%  
  
#MCD 96.16 -1.02%  
  
#MDLZ 34.36 -0.99%  
  
#MMM 164.21 -1.16%  
  
#MO 51.60 -0.91%  
  
#MRK 56.45 -1.13%  
  
#MSFT 41.68 0.38%  
  
#NG 2.819 -1.03%  
  
#NOK 7.66 -1.43%  
  
#ORAN 15.90 -1.76%  
  
#PFE 34.16 -0.67%  
  
#PG 82.83 -0.83%  
  
#QQQ 106.78 0.17%  
  
#S 5.06 -1.19%  
  
#SNE 26.74 3.48%  
  
#SPY 207.90 -0.32%  
  
#T 32.90 -0.46%  
  
#UL 42.51 -0.40%  
  
#UTX 119.82 -0.14%  
  
#VZ 48.94 -0.65%  
  
#WMT 82.59 -0.82%  
  
#XOM 84.07 -0.80%  
  
AUDCAD 0.9725 -0.14%  
  
AUDCHF 0.7615 -0.57%  
  
AUDJPY 92.12 -0.29%  
  
AUDUSD 0.7603 -0.19%  
  
CADCHF 0.7827 -0.42%  
  
CADJPY 94.69 -0.14%  
  
CHFJPY 120.86 0.28%  
  
CRSIDX 10208.2 0.20%  
  
EURAUD 1.3962 0.39%  
  
EURGBP 0.7232 0.71%  
  
NZDCAD 0.9332 -0.17%  
  
NZDCHF 0.7308 -0.60%  
  
NZDJPY 88.40 -0.32%  
  
SILVER 15.48 -0.26%  
  
Powered by CorsaCapital
